<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Development :: Rbcli Documentation</title>
    <link>https://akhoury6.github.io/rbcli/development/index.html</link>
    <description>Want to make Rbcli even better? On behalf of all Rbcli users everywhere, it’s much appreciated. Of course, even if you keep your changes to yourself and don’t contribute back, now that you’re a ninja you’ll likely want to pave your own road forward. This section will guide you how.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Andrew Khoury</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:11:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://akhoury6.github.io/rbcli/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contribution Guide</title>
      <link>https://akhoury6.github.io/rbcli/development/contributing/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 03:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://akhoury6.github.io/rbcli/development/contributing/index.html</guid>
      <description>Contributing to RBCli is the same as most open source projects:&#xA;Fork the repository Create your own branch Submit a pull request when ready That’s all there is to it! We’ve also kept our acceptance criteria pretty simple, as you’ll see below. Feel free to submit a pull request even if you don’t meet it if you would like your code or feature to be reviewed first; we do want to be mindful of your time and will review submissions before they are polished.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>License Info</title>
      <link>https://akhoury6.github.io/rbcli/development/license/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 19:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://akhoury6.github.io/rbcli/development/license/index.html</guid>
      <description>How Rbcli is Licensed We want to help the developer community build tooling faster and with less work. That’s why Rbcli was built. And let’s face it - most of us aren’t lawyers, and don’t want to worry about legal fine print when building awesome software. That’s why Rbcli is released under the MIT License. So you’re free to use Rbcli as you see fit to write your software.&#xA;MIT License: https://mit-license.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://akhoury6.github.io/rbcli/development/code_of_conduct/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 19:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://akhoury6.github.io/rbcli/development/code_of_conduct/index.html</guid>
      <description>Contributor Covenant Code of Conduct Our Pledge We as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance, race, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.&#xA;We pledge to act and interact in ways that contribute to an open, welcoming, diverse, inclusive, and healthy community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changelog</title>
      <link>https://akhoury6.github.io/rbcli/development/changelog/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://akhoury6.github.io/rbcli/development/changelog/index.html</guid>
      <description>Rbcli Changelog 0.4.0 (May 7, 2024) This release is a major refactor! Nearly all of the codebase has been rewritten from the ground up. This brought lots of features and improvements, with a heavy focus on making the framework easier to understand and use. It’s memory footprint has been reduced, and execution time has sped up too.&#xA;NOTE: The license for this version has been changed from GPLv3 to MIT.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>