<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rbcli Documentation</title>
    <link>https://akhoury6.github.io/rbcli/index.html</link>
    <description>Rbcli is a framework to quickly develop advanced command-line tools in Ruby. It has been written from the ground up with the needs of the modern technologist in mind, designed to make advanced CLI tool development as painless as possible. In Rbcli, low-level code has been wrapped and/or replaced with higher-level methods. Much of the functionality has even been reduced to single methods: for example, it takes just one declaration to define, load, and generate a user’s config file at the appropriate times.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Andrew Khoury</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 21:03:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://akhoury6.github.io/rbcli/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quick Reference</title>
      <link>https://akhoury6.github.io/rbcli/quick_reference/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 21:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://akhoury6.github.io/rbcli/quick_reference/index.html</guid>
      <description>Installation Rbcli is available on rubygems.org. You can add it to your application’s Gemfile or gemspec:&#xA;spec.add_dependency &#39;rbcli&#39;, &#39;~&gt; 0.4&#39;Or install it manually by running:&#xA;gem install rbcliStarting a Project Rbcli includes a tool to quickly create either a gem or a portable executable. Creating either is simple.&#xA;rbcli gem mytoolrbcli portable mytool rbcli portable -a mytool # Adds annotationsOr you can DIY&#xA;#!/usr/bin/env ruby require &#39;rbcli&#39; Rbcli::Configurate.cli do appname &#39;mytool&#39; version &#39;0.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Development</title>
      <link>https://akhoury6.github.io/rbcli/development/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 15:27:12 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://akhoury6.github.io/rbcli/development/index.html</guid>
      <description>Want to make Rbcli even better? On behalf of all Rbcli users everywhere, it’s much appreciated. Of course, even if you keep your changes to yourself and don’t contribute back, now that you’re a ninja you’ll likely want to pave your own road forward. This section will guide you how.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Letter To You</title>
      <link>https://akhoury6.github.io/rbcli/whoami/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 15:46:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://akhoury6.github.io/rbcli/whoami/index.html</guid>
      <description>My Fellow Coder,&#xA;I’m glad to see you are interested in Rbcli. I’d like to introduce myself. My name is Andrew, and I’ve been a technologist since 1992 when my father bought our first family computer – a 486DX2 which ran at 66Mhz (33Mhz if you turned off the ’turbo’ button) and came with MS DOS 5.0, QBasic, and a game already coded in it called Nibbles (if you care to see the code, die 5 times and don’t play again).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>